goingup.com 2011-10-08

# FREE Web Stats and Analytics, Page Rank, SEO Optimization, Website Tools and Search Engine Marketing - Are you GoingUp?

## GoingUp! Privacy Policy

GoingUp! (GU!) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website, as well as our customers and clients. GU! has established this Privacy Policy to explain what information we collect through this website and how it is used. 

In this policy, "GU!" refers to GU! staff, board members, cooperating attorneys, interns, volunteers, and consultants, all of whom are bound by law or contract to keep information they receive as part of their assistance to GU! confidential. 

GU! does not sell or rent information under any circumstances, and we do not share information without prior consent except as compelled by law. (See discussion below.) 

  * #### Information Gathered by GU!'s Site

For visitors to our website and sites using GoingUp! services, we log standard technical information, such as the numerical Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. You use of the GU! site or partner sites indicates your consent to the gathering of this information.

We do not use persistent cookies on this site unless you log into the Account Center or use "Remember Me" or other similar functionality. We may use session cookies from time to time. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, and use Tor if you wish to keep your IP number and other technical information anonymous. 

In addition, GU! collects and retains information you submit to us. It is up to you whether to submit information to us, and how much information to provide. If you choose to become an GU! customer or register for the GU! Subscription Service, we ask for your name, title, email address, city, state, postal code, country of residence, credit card number and phone number, and we may invite you to select a password.

  * #### GU!'s Use of Information

In general, GU! uses the information provided by you to provide you with the services you ask for, and to provide visitors with information. 

If you invite another person to join GU!, we will ask for that person's name and online contact information. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join GU!. 

We may run surveys, contests, or similar activities through this site. Such information will be used for the purposes for which it was collected. 

We look at technical information to diagnose problems with our server and to administer the GU! site. 

  * #### Disclosure of Your Information

While GU! endeavors to provide the highest level of protection for your information, **we will not disclose personally identifiable information about you** to third parties in any circumstance without your consent; or when it is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order. 

If we are required by law to disclose the information that you have submitted, we will attempt to provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made in order to give you an opportunity to object to the disclosure. We will attempt to provide this notice by email, if you have given us an email address, or by postal mail if you have entered a postal address. If you do not challenge the disclosure request, we may be legally required to turn over your information. 

In addition, we will independently object to requests for access to information about users of our site that we believe to be improper. 

#### Updating or Removing Your Information

You may choose to correct, update, or delete the membership information you have submitted to us by sending an email requesting changes to webmaster@goingup.com. Furthermore, if we inadvertently collect more personal information than intended, we endeavor to delete the extraneous information. However, please understand that deleted information may continue to persist on back-up media. 

  * #### Changes to Our Policies

GU!'s Privacy Policy may change from time to time. However, any revised privacy policy will be consistent with GU!'s mission. If we make any substantive changes to our policies, we will place notice in GU!ector and post notice of changes on this page. 

  * #### Security

GU! employs industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Information submitted through the shopping and membership processes is encrypted through a Secured Socket Layer (SSL) connections, which protects the information in transit. 

Although we make good faith efforts to store information collected by GU! in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee complete security. Information collected by GU! will be maintained for a length of time appropriate to our needs.

_Updated January 07, 2008_
